{
  "al": {
    "region": "Alabama",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "11Fh",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "R8Pk",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Sept. 14"
      },
      {
        "id": "7Bfz",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7"
      },
      {
        "id": "y42i",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters need to provide a photo copy of an approved ID with their absentee ballot application. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.sos.alabama.gov/alabama-votes/voter/voter-id)"
      },
      {
        "id": "i2Rf",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "[Absentee Voting](https://www.sos.alabama.gov/alabama-votes/voter/absentee-voting)"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "DjKf",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "State Board of Education",
        "Commissioner of Agriculture and Industries",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "Public Service Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ak": {
    "region": "Alaska",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "ETBV",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "vZFx",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "yXek",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "Bk1Y",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is requested, though some forms of nonphoto ID are also accepted. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot that automatically undergoes additional scrutiny. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.elections.alaska.gov/Core/votingatthepollsonelectionday.php)"
      },
      {
        "id": "bwU8",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.elections.alaska.gov/Core/absenteeearlyandinpersonvoting.php"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "Sk43",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "az": {
    "region": "Arizona",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Dtt5",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "vbET",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 12."
      },
      {
        "id": "iYVm",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "14pb",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required."
      },
      {
        "id": "tKKk",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.azcleanelections.gov/how-to-vote/early-voting/in-person"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "fuZ2",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "Corporation Commission",
        "Mine Inspector",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ar": {
    "region": "Arkansas",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "axuE",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "tquz",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "mkMA",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "ztah",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "Z7Mc",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.arkansas.gov/elections/voter-information/voter-registration-information/voting-in-arkansas"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "1SGN",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Public Lands Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ca": {
    "region": "California",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "dD6W",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available in some counties. "
      },
      {
        "id": "Qg2P",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "It varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "18WC",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "It varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "j1MW",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required for early voting, except for some first-time voters. [More information](https://www.sos.ca.gov/elections/voter-registration/vote-mail#vote-by-mail)"
      },
      {
        "id": "3A1G",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.ca.gov/elections/voting-info/ways-vote"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "YQaS",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Controller",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "State Board of Equalization",
        "Insurance Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "co": {
    "region": "Colorado",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "H14L",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "S12z",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "8cZ3",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "rkTy",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required to vote early. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.sos.state.co.us/pubs/elections/vote/acceptableFormsOfID.html)"
      },
      {
        "id": "TaiL",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "pm9V",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "State Board of Education",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ct": {
    "region": "Connecticut",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "nwrN",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "jton",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "N/A"
      },
      {
        "id": "R4GZ",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "ia42",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. For some first-time voters, ID is required. [Valid forms of ID](https://portal.ct.gov/SOTS/Election-Services/FAQ/FAQ---Voter-Identification)"
      },
      {
        "id": "TUk7",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://portal.ct.gov/SOTS/Election-Services/Voter-Information/Absentee-Ballot-Process"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "AaBB",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Comptroller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "de": {
    "region": "Delaware",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "cGnV",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "Rygd",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Dates and locations will be posted at least 30 days before Election Day. [Information](https://elections.delaware.gov/)"
      },
      {
        "id": "pdNC",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Dates and locations will be posted at least 30 days before Election Day. [Information](https://elections.delaware.gov/)"
      },
      {
        "id": "fBoq",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. [Valid forms of ID](https://elections.delaware.gov/information/faq/voting.shtml)"
      },
      {
        "id": "mN5o",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "mh23",
      "answer": [
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "dc": {
    "region": "District of Columbia",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "dRgC",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "5JmU",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24 for in-person absentee, Friday, Oct. 28 for early voting."
      },
      {
        "id": "UrgK",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "BSHh",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required to vote early, except for first time mail voters. [More information](https://dcboe.org/Voters/How-to-Vote/Mail-Ballot-Instructions)"
      },
      {
        "id": "7nAQ",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://earlyvoting.dcboe.org/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "q5AK",
      "answer": [
        "Mayor",
        "Attorney General",
        "City Council"
      ]
    }
  },
  "fl": {
    "region": "Florida",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "MvcX",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "BMr1",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Saturday, Oct. 29."
      },
      {
        "id": "PNfo",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5, but some counties might extend this until Sunday, Nov. 6."
      },
      {
        "id": "bwfx",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters need to provide an ID number when requesting a mail ballot. [Valid forms of ID](https://dos.myflorida.com/elections/for-voters/voting/vote-by-mail/)"
      },
      {
        "id": "DYn3",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://dos.myflorida.com/elections/for-voters/voting/early-voting-and-drop-boxes/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "Ug6S",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Chief Financial Officer",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ga": {
    "region": "Georgia",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "cEYj",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "VJ5h",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 17."
      },
      {
        "id": "SgKa",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "FcaW",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters need to provide their Georgia driver's license number or a photo copy of an approved ID with their absentee ballot application. Valid forms of ID can be found [here](https://sos.ga.gov/admin/uploads/2021_Absentee_App.9721_2.pdf)"
      },
      {
        "id": "PTcS",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "[Absentee voting in Georgia](https://sos.ga.gov/index.php/Elections/absentee_voting_in_georgia)"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "zmG7",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "Labor Commissioner",
        "Insurance Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "hi": {
    "region": "Hawaii",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "XADp",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "9p7p",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Oct. 25."
      },
      {
        "id": "nogw",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "d6YU",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required."
      },
      {
        "id": "91bz",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://elections.hawaii.gov/voting/voting-in-hawaii/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "ufVM",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Office of Hawaiian Affairs",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "id": {
    "region": "Idaho",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "NSvb",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available in some counties. "
      },
      {
        "id": "PTs3",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "NKng",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "Em7Q",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. [Valid forms of ID](https://voteidaho.gov/identification-requirements/)"
      },
      {
        "id": "VesD",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "DX7x",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Controller",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "il": {
    "region": "Illinois",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Q9wa",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes, early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "WMUF",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Sept. 29."
      },
      {
        "id": "6hVd",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "s7mX",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required to vote early. ID is only required when registering to vote."
      },
      {
        "id": "yyTT",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://elections.il.gov/votingandregistrationsystems/beforeelectionday.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "2onc",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Comptroller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "in": {
    "region": "Indiana",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "qtmr",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "UqR5",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 12."
      },
      {
        "id": "3kB9",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7, 12 p.m."
      },
      {
        "id": "DNUf",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.in.gov/sos/elections/voter-information/photo-id-law/)"
      },
      {
        "id": "1ubd",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.in.gov/sos/elections/voter-information/ways-to-vote/absentee-voting/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "jYVA",
      "answer": [
        "Secretary of State",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ia": {
    "region": "Iowa",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "T95U",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "yyep",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "T47i",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "u5mP",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters must provide their ID number when requesting an absentee ballot. [Valid forms of ID](https://sos.iowa.gov/elections/voterinformation/voterIDfaq.html#17)"
      },
      {
        "id": "EyRR",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.iowa.gov/elections/electioninfo/absenteeinperson.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "KuRo",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Secretary of Agriculture",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ks": {
    "region": "Kansas",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "XNeM",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "pggc",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Can start as early as Wednesday, Oct. 19, but no later than Tuesday, Nov. 1. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "QyWp",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "fWqk",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters need to provide their Kansas driver's license number or a photo copy of an approved ID with their application for an advanced ballot by mail.  Valid forms of ID](https://www.kssos.org/forms/elections/AV1.pdf)."
      },
      {
        "id": "NiUo",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://kcdcinfo.ks.gov/voter-registration-and-advanced-voting"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "k7G4",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "State Board of Education",
        "Insurance Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ky": {
    "region": "Kentucky",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "MND1",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "mWYh",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Nov. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "2rh9",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "V9Ni",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a provisional ballot, but must provide valid ID to their county clerk's office at a later date in order for their ballot to be counted. [Valid forms of ID](https://elect.ky.gov/Frequently-Asked-Questions/Documents/SB%202%20FAQ.pdf)"
      },
      {
        "id": "TBjo",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://elect.ky.gov/Voters/Pages/Absentee-Voting.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "t4u2",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "la": {
    "region": "Louisiana",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "LnXe",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "vkGG",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 26."
      },
      {
        "id": "33eb",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Dec. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "YrjV",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.sos.la.gov/ElectionsAndVoting/Vote/VoteOnElectionDay/Pages/default.aspx)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5Zrn",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.la.gov/ElectionsAndVoting/Vote/VoteEarly/Pages/default.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "JHg9",
      "answer": [
        "Public Service Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "me": {
    "region": "Maine",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "zqL2",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "6Jvj",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Friday, Oct. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "F3AJ",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Nov. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "FA8J",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first-time voters. [More information](https://apps.web.maine.gov/cgi-bin/online/AbsenteeBallot/index.pl)"
      },
      {
        "id": "zoga",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.maine.gov/sos/cec/elec/voter-info/absenteeguide.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "FwTH",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "md": {
    "region": "Maryland",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "6Jxe",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "VxQN",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Oct. 27."
      },
      {
        "id": "5Gi2",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Nov. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "Df5L",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required."
      },
      {
        "id": "xUXo",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://elections.maryland.gov/voting/early_voting.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "TJSa",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Comptroller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ma": {
    "region": "Massachusetts",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "hi8z",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "bep2",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "ye8B",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7 at 12 p.m."
      },
      {
        "id": "JjhE",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first-time voters. [More information](https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ele/eleidreq/idrequirementsidx.htm)"
      },
      {
        "id": "MKsj",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ele/eleabsentee/absidx.htm"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "6auD",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Governor's Council",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "mi": {
    "region": "Michigan",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "6vqW",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "VQ34",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Sept. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "zR3k",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "JR5u",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. [Valid forms of ID](https://mvic.sos.state.mi.us/Home/VoteInPerson/#id-required)"
      },
      {
        "id": "1Pei",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://mvic.sos.state.mi.us/Home/VoteAtHome"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "CDbe",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "mn": {
    "region": "Minnesota",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "4szp",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "SRQQ",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Sept. 23."
      },
      {
        "id": "9L8A",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "pXZy",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required."
      },
      {
        "id": "s6TH",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.state.mn.us/elections-voting/other-ways-to-vote/vote-early-in-person/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "aooY",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Auditor",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ms": {
    "region": "Mississippi",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "j9kV",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "BkeP",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Sept. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "EEXk",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "jNGv",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.sos.ms.gov/content/documents/elections/Mississippi%20Voter%20Information%20Guide%202022.pdf)"
      },
      {
        "id": "ZZ6H",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.ms.gov/content/documents/elections/Mississippi%20Voter%20Information%20Guide%202022.pdf"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "UmaS",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "mo": {
    "region": "Missouri",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "jRc6",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "kYbT",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Sept. 20."
      },
      {
        "id": "x76w",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "xHhi",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.sos.mo.gov/elections/goVoteMissouri/howtovote#Absentee)"
      },
      {
        "id": "SGEZ",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.mo.gov/elections/goVoteMissouri/howtovote#absentee"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "TNSC",
      "answer": [
        "Auditor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "mt": {
    "region": "Montana",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "9XQR",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "PS1h",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Tuesday, Oct. 11."
      },
      {
        "id": "87AN",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "QYvd",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required. ID is only required when registering to vote."
      },
      {
        "id": "w4RX",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sosmt.gov/elections/faq/#absentee-voting"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "UVzh",
      "answer": [
        "Public Service Commissioner",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ne": {
    "region": "Nebraska",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "kiWc",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "HC9Y",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Oct. 11."
      },
      {
        "id": "f2L5",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "AbWB",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first time voters."
      },
      {
        "id": "396N",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.nebraska.gov/elections/early-voting"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "3LX2",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "State Board of Education",
        "Public Service Commissioner",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "nv": {
    "region": "Nevada",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "33Zh",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "LVXN",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Oct. 22."
      },
      {
        "id": "nn6S",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "kuM8",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first time voters. [More information](https://www.nvsos.gov/sos/elections/voters/mail-ballot-voting)"
      },
      {
        "id": "rbpJ",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.nvsos.gov/sos/elections/voters/early-voting-information"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "ks5q",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Controller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "nh": {
    "region": "New Hampshire",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "dqCU",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "zmw9",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Sunday, Oct. 9."
      },
      {
        "id": "tT1u",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "btRW",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. Unless voter did not provide ID when registering to vote. "
      },
      {
        "id": "RZAt",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "B9GS",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "State Executive Council",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "nj": {
    "region": "New Jersey",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "fqSr",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "K5b2",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Oct. 29."
      },
      {
        "id": "fnkM",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "ahZP",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first time voters. "
      },
      {
        "id": "ZrdS",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.state.nj.us/state/elections/vote-early-voting.shtml"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "AcCw",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "nm": {
    "region": "New Mexico",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "VUa7",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "SWCw",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Oct. 11."
      },
      {
        "id": "wPKs",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "mRaH",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first-time voters. [More information](https://www.sos.state.nm.us/voting-and-elections/voting-faqs/voting/)"
      },
      {
        "id": "X2vw",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.state.nm.us/voting-and-elections/voting-faqs/early-voting-in-person/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "3Nex",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Public Education Commission",
        "Public Lands Commissioner",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ny": {
    "region": "New York",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "CfjU",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "icez",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Oct. 29."
      },
      {
        "id": "p9f3",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Sunday, Nov. 6."
      },
      {
        "id": "ES9d",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. No document is required to vote, unless you are a first-time voter and ID was not provided upon registration.  "
      },
      {
        "id": "Uc8c",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.elections.ny.gov/VotingAbsentee.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "NRhQ",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Comptroller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "nc": {
    "region": "North Carolina",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "gn1E",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "gieJ",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Oct. 20."
      },
      {
        "id": "FyHh",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "xVb6",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required when applying for an absentee ballot. [More information](https://www.ncsbe.gov/voting/vote-mail/detailed-instructions-vote-mail#1-request-ballot)"
      },
      {
        "id": "vpdN",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.ncsbe.gov/voting/vote-early-person"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "n6T4",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "nd": {
    "region": "North Dakota",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "RTmY",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "4qff",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies by county, early voting may begin 15 days before the election. Check with your local election office."
      },
      {
        "id": "5LKe",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "AD7j",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. If a voter is not able to provide valid ID, they may cast a ballot that is securely set aside until the individual can provide proper identification. [Valid forms of ID](https://vote.nd.gov/IDRequirements.aspx)"
      },
      {
        "id": "o3RY",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "euhL",
      "answer": [
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "Public Service Commission",
        "Tax Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "oh": {
    "region": "Ohio",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "w7Ec",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "r9FE",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 12."
      },
      {
        "id": "tkvd",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7 at 2 p.m."
      },
      {
        "id": "M2XL",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required when requesting an absentee ballot. [More information](https://www.ohiosos.gov/elections/voters/absentee-voting/)"
      },
      {
        "id": "aYRK",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.ohiosos.gov/elections/voters/toolkit/early-voting/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "Xzm4",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "State Board of Education",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ok": {
    "region": "Oklahoma",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "wyoU",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "aaZJ",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Nov. 2."
      },
      {
        "id": "VZaU",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "knCv",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID or voter identification card is required. [Valid forms of ID](https://oklahoma.gov/elections/voters/proof-of-identity.html)"
      },
      {
        "id": "nTVn",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://oklahoma.gov/elections/voters/early-voting.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "ypWD",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "Corporation Commissioner",
        "Insurance Commissioner",
        "Labor Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "or": {
    "region": "Oregon",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "bxCb",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "No."
      },
      {
        "id": "7Y1Q",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "N/A"
      },
      {
        "id": "qECn",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "N/A"
      },
      {
        "id": "cfSo",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is required when registering to vote. [More information](https://sos.oregon.gov/voting/pages/registration.aspx?lang=en)"
      },
      {
        "id": "8KsE",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "Mqa5",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Labor Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "pa": {
    "region": "Pennsylvania",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "kbDS",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "CHi8",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Sept. 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "DGUM",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Nov. 1."
      },
      {
        "id": "4nga",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required when applying for an absentee ballot. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.vote.pa.gov/Voting-in-PA/Pages/Mail-and-Absentee-Ballot.aspx#id-mail)"
      },
      {
        "id": "cSwp",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.vote.pa.gov/Voting-in-PA/Pages/Early-Voting.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "exue",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ri": {
    "region": "Rhode Island",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "C6Nd",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "MaHx",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "bN4v",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 11."
      },
      {
        "id": "sBBw",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a provisional ballot. [Valid forms of ID](https://elections.ri.gov/voting/id.php)"
      },
      {
        "id": "dEKu",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://vote.sos.ri.gov/Voter/PersonVotingPage"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "Gxas",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "sc": {
    "region": "South Carolina",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "vDUB",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "Wf8V",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Oct. 25"
      },
      {
        "id": "HXob",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "LUbT",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.scvotes.gov/node/235)"
      },
      {
        "id": "tgUa",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "jpJ5",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Comptroller",
        "Superintendent of Education",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "sd": {
    "region": "South Dakota",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "vkTn",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "ABAF",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Sept. 23."
      },
      {
        "id": "jjCH",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "So1s",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is requested when submitting an absentee ballot application. If ID is not provided, voters can have their application notarized. [More information](https://sdsos.gov/elections-voting/voting/absentee-voting.aspx)"
      },
      {
        "id": "qbnc",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sdsos.gov/elections-voting/voting/absentee-voting.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "rGxk",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "State Auditor",
        "State Treasurer",
        "Public Utilities Commissioner",
        "Commissioner of School and Public Lands",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "tn": {
    "region": "Tennessee",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "iVCA",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "bbiF",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "e2X3",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Nov. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "exn5",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "ki49",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.tn.gov/elections/guides/how-to-early-vote-in-person"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "yDne",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "tx": {
    "region": "Texas",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "JBdE",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "qroP",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "bChh",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "1jwv",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required when applying for an absentee ballot and when returning completed ballot. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.votetexas.gov/voting-by-mail/index.html)"
      },
      {
        "id": "HYo2",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.votetexas.gov/faq/early-voting.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "iChU",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Comptroller",
        "Land Office Commissioner",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "Railroad Commissioner",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "ut": {
    "region": "Utah",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "5T7E",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "1p9T",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "uv2d",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "yqYt",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "qcMz",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "Gdnb",
      "answer": [
        "Treasurer",
        "U.S Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "vt": {
    "region": "Vermont",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Drsx",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "4u2W",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "a9e8",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "TNQg",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID not required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "z9Dr",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.vermont.gov/elections/voters/early-absentee-voting/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "eD3v",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "State Auditor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "va": {
    "region": "Virginia",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "VehL",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "kKu2",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Sept. 23."
      },
      {
        "id": "wujb",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "ezfq",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. [Valid forms of ID](https://www.elections.virginia.gov/media/formswarehouse/voter-id/outreach-materials/documents/Voter-Identification-Chart-Rev-4-28-21.pdf)"
      },
      {
        "id": "Lm7p",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.elections.virginia.gov/casting-a-ballot/absentee-voting/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "4zL2",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "wa": {
    "region": "Washington",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "EWpJ",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "z6fQ",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Oct. 21."
      },
      {
        "id": "5znG",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "kVfe",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "y19e",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.wa.gov/elections/faq_vote_by_mail.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "dpau",
      "answer": [
        "Secretary of State",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "wv": {
    "region": "West Virginia",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "UPhN",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "wBzK",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 26."
      },
      {
        "id": "kcLX",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "bqEC",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a provisional ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. [Valid forms of ID](https://sos.wv.gov/elections/Pages/BeReg.aspx)"
      },
      {
        "id": "eRFS",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "http://www.wvlegislature.gov/wvcode/ChapterEntire.cfm?chap=3&art=3&section=3"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "tsNy",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "wi": {
    "region": "Wisconsin",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "EWaL",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "rVqq",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies by county. "
      },
      {
        "id": "G3Fx",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies by county. "
      },
      {
        "id": "B2Ws",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a provisional ballot, but must provide valid ID to their municipal clerk at a later date in order for their ballot to be counted. [Valid forms of ID](https://myvote.wi.gov/Portals/0/Documents/gab_123is_provisional_voting_information_sheet_20_31072.pdf)"
      },
      {
        "id": "2FnS",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://my.lwv.org/wisconsin/local-absentee-ballot-return-and-early-voting-locations"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "HrRf",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Secretary of State",
        "State Treasurer",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  },
  "wy": {
    "region": "Wyoming",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "hKUw",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "BdU4",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Sept. 23."
      },
      {
        "id": "mz9x",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "ogi3",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. [Valid forms of ID](https://sos.wyo.gov/faqs.aspx?root=ELEC)"
      },
      {
        "id": "G45n",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "fVwp",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "State Auditor",
        "State Treasurer",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    }
  }
}
